A Guide to the Barksdale Theatre Records 1945-2006 (bulk 1954-2004)
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Production files, 1954-2000., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 28-37)
  - Boys and Girls Together Undated (Box-folder 37:8)
  - Gift of the Magi Undated (Box-folder 37:9)
    Correspondence, sketches, and script
  - Take a giant step Advertisement Undated (Box-folder 37:9a)
  - Audition forms (blank) Undated (Box-folder 37:10)
- Series VII. Programs, 1954-2004., Extent: 3.15 cu. ft. (9 boxes). (Box 38-46)
  The Programs Series is housed in 9 boxes and arranged chronologically with the year in parenthesis indicating the date of the opening. Included are programs for a majority of the Barksdale shows, 1954-2004. Also included are a few flyers and leaflets for the earlier dates. The series also includes a box of miscellaneous programs from a variety of theatres including Barter Theatre, Richmond City Works, Richmond Symphony, Swift Creek Mill Playhouse, Theatre IV, and Theatre Virginia, 1959-1999.
  - Gold in the Hills 1954 September (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Spring season program 1955 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Fall season program 1955 (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Biography 1956 September (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Don Juan in Hell 1956 October (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Present Laughter 1956 November (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Silas, The Chore Boy 1956 November (Box-folder 38:7)
  - Spring season program 1956 (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Winter season program 1956 (Box-folder 38:9)
  - White Sheep of the Family 1957 March (Box-folder 38:10)
  - To Rise One Day 1957 May (Box-folder 38:11)
  - Dirty Work at the Crossroads 1957 September (Box-folder 38:12)
  - Dangerous Corner 1957 October (Box-folder 38:13)
  - Fall/Winter season program 1957 (Box-folder 38:14)
  - The Matchmaker 1958 June (Box-folder 38:15)
  - The Fourposter 1958 September (Box-folder 38:16)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace 1958 November (Box-folder 38:16a)
  - Fall/Winter season program 1958 (Box-folder 38:17)
  - For Love or Money 1959 March (Box-folder 38:17a)
  - The Little Hut 1959 July (Box-folder 38:17b)
  - Where's Charley? 1959 September (Box-folder 38:18)
  - Winter/Spring season program 1959 (Box-folder 38:19)
  - 1960 Winter/Spring season program 1959 Fall (Box-folder 38:20)
  - The Crucible c. 1959-1960 (Box-folder 38:20a)
  - Romanoff and Juliet 1960 February (Box-folder 38:20b)
  - Venus Observed 1960 March (Box-folder 38:20c)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire 1960 April (Box-folder 38:20d)
  - Picnic 1960 September (Box-folder 38:21)
    Original sketches used in program located in Oversize Series (XI) Subseries 1 Artwork
  - Abie's Irish Rose 1960 November (Box-folder 38:21a)
  - Two for the See-Saw 1961 May (Box-folder 38:22)
  - Mister Roberts 1961 October (Box-folder 38:23)
  - J.B. 1962 May (Box-folder 38:24)
  - Once Upon a Mattress 1962 September (Box-folder 38:25)
  - The Curious Savage 1963 June (Box-folder 38:25a)
  - The Fantasticks 1963 September (Box-folder 38:26)
  - A Shot in the Dark 1963 December (Box-folder 38:26a)
  - The Moon is Blue 1964 February (Box-folder 38:26b)
  - Gideon 1964 April (Box-folder 38:27)
  - The Boy Friend 1964 October (Box-folder 38:28)
  - The Marriage-Go-Round 1965 September (Box-folder 38:29)
  - Never Too Late 1965 October (Box-folder 38:30)
  - Season program 1965 (Box-folder 38:31)
  - Never Too Late 1966 January (Box-folder 38:32)
  - Little Mary Sunshine 1966 April (Box-folder 38:32a)
  - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Strawberry Banks) 1966 May (Box-folder 38:33)
  - Critic's Choice (Strawberry Banks) 1966 June (Box-folder 38:34)
  - The Typist and the Tiger 1966 June (Box-folder 38:34a)
  - Janus (Strawberry Banks) 1966 July (Box-folder 38:35)
  - Any Wednesday 1966 September (Box-folder 38:36)
  - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off 1966 October (Box-folder 38:37)
  - Season program 1966 (Box-folder 38:38)
  - The Night of the Iguana 1967 April (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Gold in the Hills (Strawberry Banks) 1967 May (Box-folder 39:2)
  - The Champagne Complex 1967 June (Box-folder 39:3)
  - The Happy Time (Strawberry Banks) 1967 June (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Luv (Strawberry Banks) 1967 July (Box-folder 39:5)
  - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off (Guest production at the Barter Theatre, Abingdon, Va.) 1967 August (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Barefoot in the Park 1967 July (Box-folder 39:7)
  - The Owl and the Pussycat 1967 November (Box-folder 39:8)
  - Generation 1968 January (Box-folder 39:9)
  - One Hundred and Some 1968 March (Box-folder 39:10)
  - Rattle of a Simple Man 1968 May (Box-folder 39:11)
  - Oliver 1968 July (Box-folder 39:12)
  - The Impossible Years 1968 September (Box-folder 39:13)
  - Irma La Douce 1968 December (Box-folder 39:14)
  - The Lion in Winter 1969 February (Box-folder 39:15)
  - Philadelphia, Here I Come 1969 April (Box-folder 39:16)
  - The Fantasticks 1969 June (Box-folder 39:17)
  - Cactus Flower 1969 July (Box-folder 39:18)
  - The Absence of a Cello 1969 October (Box-folder 39:19)
  - Annie, Get Your Gun 1969 November (Box-folder 39:20)
  - The Hostage 1970 March (Box-folder 39:21)
  - Tons of Money 1970 April (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Man of La Mancha 1970 June (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Money 1970 September (Box-folder 40:3)
  - I do! I do! 1970 October (Box-folder 40:4)
  - The Boys in the Band 1971 February (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Three Men on a Horse 1971 April (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Plaza Suite 1971 May (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Sound of Music 1971 July (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Old Wives' Tale 1971 October (Box-folder 40:9)
  - You're a good man, Charlie Brown 1971 November (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Goodbye Charlie 1972 February (Box-folder 40:11)
  - Never Too Late 1972 April (Box-folder 40:12)
  - Butterflies are free 1972 June (Box-folder 40:13)
  - George Washington Slept Here 1972 August (Box-folder 40:14)
  - Gypsy 1972 November (Box-folder 40:15)
  - To be young, gifted, and black 1973 February (Box-folder 40:16)
  - The Odd Couple 1973 April (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Dracula 1973 June (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Three Bags Full 1973 August (Box-folder 41:3)
  - The Patriots 1973 October (Box-folder 41:4)
  - Barefoot in the Park 1973 December (Box-folder 41:5)
  - The Front Page 1974 February (Box-folder 41:6)
  - Does a Tiger Wear a Necktie? 1974 April (Box-folder 41:7)
  - Dames At Sea 1974 April (Box-folder 41:8)
  - You Can't Take it With You 1974 August (Box-folder 41:9)
  - Long Day's Journey Into Night 1974 September (Box-folder 41:10)
  - A Flea in Her Ear 1974 November (Box-folder 41:11)
  - That Championship Season 1975 January (Box-folder 41:12)
  - Godspell 1975 March (Box-folder 41:13)
  - Catch Me if You Can 1975 August (Box-folder 41:14)
  - Ah, Wilderness! 1975 October (Box-folder 41:15)
  - Ladies in Retirement 1976 January (Box-folder 41:16)
  - Unhealthy to be Unpleasant (UTBU) 1976 March (Box-folder 41:17)
  - My Fat Friend 1976 May (Box-folder 42:1)
  - I Never Sang For My Father and Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead 1976 July (Box-folder 42:2)
  - How the other half lives 1976 September (Box-folder 42:3)
  - You can't take it with you 1976 November (Box-folder 42:4)
  - Visit to a small planet 1977 February (Box-folder 42:5)
  - The Royal Family 1977 November (Box-folder 42:6)
  - The River Niger (Box-folder 42:7)
  - Equus 1978 February (Box-folder 42:8)
  - The Little Hut 1978 April (Box-folder 42:9)
  - Man of La Mancha 1978 July (Box-folder 42:10)
  - Diamond Studs 1978 October (Box-folder 42:11)
  - One flew over the cuckoo's nest 1979 February (Box-folder 42:12)
  - The Good Doctor 1979 April (Box-folder 42:13)
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner 1979 June (Box-folder 42:14)
  - Old Wives' Tale 1979 August (Box-folder 42:15)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest 1979 October (Box-folder 42:16)
  - Light up the sky 1980 February (Box-folder 42:17)
  - Murder at the Howard Johnson's 1980 May (Box-folder 42:18)
  - The Mikado 1980 July (Box-folder 42:19)
  - Chapter Two 1980 October (Box-folder 42:20)
  - The 1940's radio hour 1980 December (Box-folder 42:21)
  - Da 1981 February (Box-folder 42:22)
  - Any number can die 1981 April (Box-folder 42:23)
  - H.M.S. Pinafore 1981 June (Box-folder 42:24)
  - Bad day at Black Rock 1981 October (Box-folder 42:25)
  - Blithe Spirit 1981 December (Box-folder 43:1)
  - Much ado about Nothing 1982 February (Box-folder 43:2)
  - The Elephant Man 1982 April (Box-folder 43:3)
  - The Pirates of Penzance 1982 June (Box-folder 43:4)
  - Sweeney Todd 1982 October (Box-folder 43:5)
  - George Washington slept here 1983 February (Box-folder 43:6)
  - A couple of white chicks sitting around talking 1983 April (Box-folder 43:7)
  - Patience 1983 September (Box-folder 43:8)
  - What the butler saw 1983 September (Box-folder 43:9)
  - The Middle Ages 1983 November (Box-folder 43:10)
  - Present Laughter 1984 February (Box-folder 43:11)
  - Foxfire 1984 April (Box-folder 43:12)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1984 June (Box-folder 43:13)
  - Here's a How-De-Do! 1984 (Box-folder 43:14)
  - Taking my turn 1986 November (Box-folder 43:15)
  - Artichoke 1988 April (Box-folder 43:16)
  - Hot Grog 1988 June (Box-folder 43:17)
  - Painting Churches 1988 October (Box-folder 43:18)
  - Season program 1988 (Box-folder 43:18a)
  - Nunsense 1989 March (Box-folder 43:19)
  - The Mikado 1989 June (Box-folder 43:20)
  - You never can tell 1989 September (Box-folder 43:21)
  - Season program 1989 (Box-folder 43:21a)
  - Nunsense 1990 January (Box-folder 43:22)
  - The Cocktail Hour 1990 May (Box-folder 43:23)
  - Earnest in Love 1990 July (Box-folder 43:24)
  - On the Verge 1990 September (Box-folder 43:25)
  - Season program 1990 (Box-folder 43:25a)
  - Home Games 1991 January (Box-folder 43:26)
  - This Lady's Not for Burning 1991 May (Box-folder 43:27)
  - The Zulu and the Zada 1991 September (Box-folder 43:28)
  - Oh Coward! 1991 November (Box-folder 43:29)
  - Season program 1991 (Box-folder 43:29a)
  - American Beauty 1992 March (Box-folder 43:30)
  - The Road to Mecca 1992 May (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Lucky Stiff 1992 July (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Twelfth Night 1992 October (Box-folder 44:3)
  - Social security 1992 November (Box-folder 44:4)
  - Season program 1992 (Box-folder 44:4a)
  - Death of a Salesman 1993 February (Box-folder 44:5)
  - By Strouse 1993 March (Box-folder 44:6)
  - Oh dad, Poor dad, Mamma's hung you in the closet and I'm feelin' so sad 1993 May (Box-folder 44:7)
  - Bojangles 1993 July (Box-folder 44:8)
  - The Voice of the Turtle 1993 September (Box-folder 44:9)
  - Godspell 1993 November (Box-folder 44:10)
  - Season program 1993 (Box-folder 44:10a)
  - Our Town 1994 January (Box-folder 44:11)
  - Falsettos 1994 March (Box-folder 44:12)
  - Love letters 1994 April (Box-folder 44:13)
  - A day in Hollywood/A night in the Ukraine 1994 June (Box-folder 44:14)
  - Zelda: The last flapper 1994 July (Box-folder 44:15)
  - Talley's Folly 1994 August (Box-folder 44:16)
  - The Turn of the Screw 1994 August (Box-folder 44:17)
  - The World Goes Round 1994 November (Box-folder 44:18)
  - Season program 1994 (Box-folder 44:19)
  - Season program 1994-1995 (Box-folder 44:20)
  - Born Yesterday 1995 January (Box-folder 44:20a)
  - Oleanna 1995 August (Box-folder 44:21)
  - Nunsense 1995 September (Box-folder 44:22)
  - The Search for Signs of Intelligent Life in the Universe 1995 September (Box-folder 44:23)
  - Talking with... 1996 February (Box-folder 44:24)
  - The Trip to Bountiful 1996 March (Box-folder 44:25)
  - Oil City Symphony 1996 May (Box-folder 44:26)
  - Das Barbecu 1996 July (Box-folder 44:27)
  - The Taffetas 1996 November (Box-folder 44:28)
  - Season program 1996 (Box-folder 44:28a)
  - The House of Blue Leaves 1997 January (Folder 44:29)
  - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) 1997 February (Box-folder 44:30)
  - Molly Sweeney 1997 May (Box-folder 44:31)
  - Blues in the Night 1997 June (Box-folder 44:32)
  - Love! Valour! Compassion! 1997 August (Box-folder 44:33)
  - The Woman in Black 1997 September (Box-folder 44:34)
  - Red, Hot, and Cole 1997 November (Box-folder 44:35)
  - Season program 1997 (Box-folder 44:36)
  - From the Mississippi Delta 1998 March (Box-folder 44:37)
  - The Young Man from Atlanta 1998 April (Box-folder 45:1)
  - The Rocky Horror Picture Show 1998 May (Box-folder 45:2)
  - Inherit the Wind 1998 September (Box-folder 45:3)
  - She loves me 1998 November (Box-folder 45:4)
  - Season program 1998 (Box-folder 45:5)
  - The Sisters Rosensweig 1999 January (Box-folder 45:6)
  - The Old Settler 1999 February (Box-folder 45:7)
  - Ella and Her Fella, Frank 1999 November (Box-folder 45:8)
  - Season program 1999 (Box-folder 45:9)
  - The Queen of Bingo 2000 January (Box-folder 45:10)
  - The Side Man 2000 February (Box-folder 45:11)
  - Full Gallop 2000 April (Box-folder 45:12)
  - Carousel 2000 November (Box-folder 45:13)
  - Season program 2000-2001 (Box-folder 45:14)
  - Misfits 2001 January (Box-folder 45:15)
  - Taming of the Shrew 2001 March (Box-folder 45:16)
  - They're playing our song (Theatre IV) 2001 June (Box-folder 45:17)
  - Light up the sky 2004 June (Box-folder 45:18)
  - The Gift of the Magi, A Christmas Carol Undated (Box-folder 45:19)
  - Upstage for Kids 1996-1997 (Box-folder 45:20)
  - Programs from various theatres 1959-1999 (Box 46)
- Series VIII. Theatre Management Records, 1954-2001., Extent: 3.15 cu. ft. (9 boxes). (Box 47-55)
  The Theatre Management Records Series is housed in 9 boxes and arranged alphabetically into four subseries. Subseries have been designated for Administrative files, Board of Trustees files, Employment files and resumes, and Marketing and advertising.
  - Subseries 1: Administrative files ca. 1954-2000
    This subseries is housed in 2 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included are articles of incorporation, brochures, bylaws, calendars, contracts, envelopes, legal papers, notebooks, speeches, and pamphlets regarding workers compensation laws. Of note are the brochures on the Barksdale Theatre and Hanover Tavern, ca. 1960-1990.
    - Articles of incorporation and bylaws 1973-1994 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Automobiles 1991 (Box-folder 47:2)
    - Barksdale Art Festival 1967 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - Barksdale Theatre Club ca. 1954 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - Brochures ca. 1960-1990 (Box-folder 47:5)
      Includes brochures on Historic Hanover County and brochures from the Barksdale Theatre. Also includes postcards and printed sketches of Hanover Tavern.
    - Calendar 1980 (Box-folder 47:6)
    - Calendar 1999 (Box-folder 47:7)
    - Calendar n.d. (Box-folder 47:8)
    - Complementary V.I.P. seating request form (blank) n.d. (Box-folder 47:9)
    - Contracts 1974-2000 (Box-folder 47:10)
    - Envelopes, blank n.d. (Box-folder 47:11)
    - Lawsuits, Catering by Jill vs. Barksdale Theatre 1994 (Box-folder 47:12)
    - Lawsuits, Miscellaneous 1994 (Box-folder 47:13)
    - Notebook n.d. (Box-folder 47:14)
    - Notebook n.d. (Box-folder 48:1)
    - Notes n.d. (Box-folder 48:2)
    - Production supplies 1994-1997 (Box-folder 48:3)
    - Speeches ca. 1997 (Box-folder 48:4)
    - Staff contact list n.d. (Box-folder 48:5)
    - Staff meeting 1997 (Box-folder 48:6)
    - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), Survey 1995 (Box-folder 48:7)
    - Virginia ABC 1999-2000 (Box-folder 48:8)
    - Workers compensation forms (blank) and pamphlet ca. 1990 (Box-folder 48:9)
  - Subseries 2: Board of Trustees Files 1986-2000
    This subseries is housed in 4 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. This subseries includes mainly minute files of the Board of Trustees for both the Barksdale Theatre and the Hanover Tavern Foundation. The minute files include agendas, budgets and finances, clippings, contracts, correspondence, memoranda, minutes, notes, reports, and schedules of events. Also included are the articles of incorporation and bylaws of the Hanover Tavern Foundation and lists of board members. Included is information regarding the relationship between the Barksdale Theatre and the Hanover Tavern Foundation and the lease and sale of Hanover Tavern. Topics include the renovation of Hanover Tavern, move of Barksdale Theatre to Willow Lawn Shopping Center in Richmond, catering at the Barksdale Theatre, lawsuits, finances and ticket sales, subscription renewals, and the hiring of new staff.
    - Board of trustees membership lists n.d. (Box-folder 49:1)
    - Minute files 1986 (Box-folder 49:2)
    - Minute files 1987 (Box-folder 49:3)
    - Minute files 1987-1989 (Box-folder 49:4)
    - Minute files 1987-1993 (Box-folder 49:5)
    - Minute files 1987-1993 (Box-folder 49:6)
    - Minute files 1988 (Box-folder 49:7)
    - Minute files 1989 (Box-folder 49:8)
    - Minute files 1990 (Box-folder 49:9)
    - Minute files 1991 (Box-folder 50:1)
    - Minute files 1992 January-May (Box-folder 50:2)
    - Minute files 1992 June-December (Box-folder 50:3)
    - Minute files 1993 (Box-folder 50:4)
    - Minute files 1993-1994 (Box-folder 50:5)
    - Minute files 1993-1994 (Box-folder 50:6)
    - Minute files 1993-1994 (Box-folder 51:1)
    - Minute files 1994 (Box-folder 51:2)
    - Minute files 1994-1995 (Box-folder 51:3)
    - Minute files 1994-1995 (Box-folder 51:4)
    - Minute files 1995 January-May (Box-folder 51:5)
    - Minute files 1995 June-December (Box-folder 52:1)
    - Minute files 1995 lease (Box-folder 52:2)
    - Minute files 1996 (Box-folder 52:3)
    - Minute files 1997 (Box-folder 52:4)
    - Minute files 1998 (Box-folder 52:5)
    - Minute files 1999 (Box-folder 52:6)
    - Minute files 2000 (Box-folder 52:7)
    - Report 2000 (Box-folder 52:8)
  - Subseries 3: Employment files and resumes 1991-2000
    This subseries is housed in 1 box and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included is information from the Actors' Equity Association regarding contracts and rules governing employment in dinner and small professional theatres. Included are some job descriptions and salary rates for jobs at the Barksdale, 1998-2000, and a personnel policy manual from the Barksdale, undated. The manual outlines the mission statement, employee classification, orientation and training, and employee benefits. The resumes include correspondence and photographs and are arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Actors Equity Association 1991 (Box-folder 53:1)
    - Capital Area Training Consortium 1995 (Box-folder 53:2)
    - Job descriptions and salaries 1998-2000 (Box-folder 53:3)
    - Personnel policy manual n.d. (Box-folder 53:4)
    - Resumes, A-C (Box-folder 53:5)
    - Resumes, Pat Carroll (Box-folder 53:6)
    - Resumes, D-G (Box-folder 53:7)
    - Resumes, H-I (Box-folder 53:8)
    - Resumes, J-K (Box-folder 53:9)
    - Resumes, L (Box-folder 53:10)
    - Resumes, M-P (Box-folder 53:11)
    - Resumes, r (Box-folder 53:12)
    - Resumes, S (Box-folder 53:13)
    - Resumes, T-W (Box-folder 53:14)
  - Subseries 4: Marketing and advertising 1956-2001
    This subseries is housed in 2 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included are advertisements, correspondence, logos, programs, and newsletters. Of note are the advertisements and logo sketches for Barksdale, 1993-1998, and early programs covers sponsored by Thalhimers, 1956-1957.
    - Advertisements 1993-1994 (Box-folder 54:1)
    - Advertisements, 1994-1995 Season 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54:2)
    - Advertisements, 1994-1995 Season 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54:3)
    - Advertisements, 1994-1995 Season 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - Advertisements, 1994-1995 Season 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - Advertisements, 1994-1995 Season 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54:5)
    - Advertisements, 1994-1995 Season 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54:6)
    - Advertisements, 1995-1996 Season 1995-1996 (Box-folder 54:7)
    - Advertisements 1997-1998 (Box-folder 55:1)
    - Bulk mailings 1994 (Box-folder 55:2)
    - Logos 1995 (Box-folder 55:3)
    - Slideshow n.d. (Box-folder 55:4)
    - Survey n.d. (Box-folder 55:5)
    - Thalhimers Theatre programme covers 1956-1957 (Box-folder 55:6)
    - Virginia dairy commercial n.d. (Box-folder 55:7)
- Series IX. Miscellaneous, 1945-1998., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 56-58)
  The Miscellaneous Series is housed in 3 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included are brochures, correspondence, histories, programs, and publications. Included is information on The Arts Council of Richmond, Carpenter Science Theatre Advisory Board, Glen Allen Cultural Arts Program, Richmond Alliance of Professional Theatres, and the Richmond Public Relations Association. Also included are various programs and tickets stubs from theatres in Europe, 1945, donations and correspondence to the Muriel McAuley Memorial Fund, 1998, and a eulogy for Nancy Kilgore, 1993. Of note are the histories of Hanover Tavern and markups and a draft to Going on...Barksdale Theatre The First Thirty One Years, written by Muriel McAuley. Also of note is The Mystery of Hanover Tavern, probably written by Muriel McAuley. These are recaps (4-6 pages each) of the year's events at Barksdale Theatre written as annual Christmas greetings, 1954-1958.
  - American Theatre 1997 (Box-folder 56:1)
  - The Arts Council of Richmond, Inc. 1984-1994 (Box-folder 56:2)
  - Ballet Impromptu 1959-1963 (Box-folder 56:3)
  - Bob's overseas souvenirs 1945 (Box-folder 56:4)
  - Carpenter Science Theatre Advisory Board 1996 (Box-folder 56:5)
  - Cartoons n.d. (Box-folder 56:6)
  - Certificates 1974-1987 (Box-folder 56:7)
  - Colonel Read Foundation 1995 (Box-folder 56:8)
  - Costume lecture notes 1949-1950 (Box-folder 56:9)
  - Drawings n.d. (Box-folder 56:10)
  - Drawings n.d. (Box-folder 56:11)
  - Glen Allen Cultural Arts Center 1995 (Box-folder 56:12)
  - Hanover Tavern (working draft) (Box-folder 56:13)
    History of the Hanover Tavern, written by an unknown author
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years, written by Muriel McAuley (Box-folder 56:14)
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years, written by Muriel McAuley (Box-folder 56:15)
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (drafts), written by Muriel McAuley (Box-folder 57:1)
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years, Mark up sheets (Box-folder 57:2)
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years, Mark up sheets (Box-folder 57:3)
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years, Mark up sheets (Box-folder 57:4)
  - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years, Index (draft) (Box-folder 57:5)
  - Kilgore, David "Pete", Memorial 2006 (Box-folder 57:5a)
  - McAuley, Muriel, Miscellaneous education and legal papers 1943-1987 (Box-folder 57:6)
  - McAuley, Muriel, Memorial 1998 (Box-folder 57:7)
  - Metropolitan Area Projects Strategies (MAPS) 1998 (Box-folder 57:8)
  - Metropolitan Richmond Convention and Visitors Bureau 1993-1994 (Box-folder 57:9)
  - Metropolitan Richmond Recreation Corporation 1992-1994 (Box-folder 57:10)
  - MODA 1997-1998 (Box-folder 57:11)
  - The Mystery of Hanover Tavern, probably written by Muriel McAuley 1954-1958 (Box-folder 58:1)
    These are recaps (4-6 pages each) of the year's events at Barksdale Theatre written as annual Christmas greetings
  - The Mystery of Hanover Tavern, probably written by Muriel McAuley 1954-1958 (Box-folder 58:1)
    These are recaps (4-6 pages each) of the year's events at Barksdale Theatre written as annual Christmas greetings. Includes notes to Edith Lindeman Calisch
  - Nelson, Bill, Pamphlet n.d. (Box-folder 58:3)
  - Newsletters, Ashland Chamber Voice 1993 (Box-folder 58:4)
  - Photographs ca. 1975 (Box-folder 58:5)
    Historic black and white photographs from the Valentine Museum
  - Poem n.d. (Box-folder 58:6)
  - Programs 1955-1987 (Box-folder 58:7)
  - Publications 1956-1998 (Box-folder 58:8)
  - Remembrances of Nancy Kilgore 1993 (Box-folder 58:9)
  - Richmond Alliance of Professional Theatres 1995-1998 (Box-folder 58:10)